

Ahmed Mlaouhia

Software Engineer

Software engineer specialized in Web and DevOps with much potential from React, NodeJS, Typescript and Tailwind CSS... in Web to Linux, SSH, docker, Jenkins... in DevOps. With my skills, I have the competence to deliver good quality code, test, integrate and deploy it continuously. I am a student and always looking opportunities to enhance my skills.

Contact

Phone

+216 23 646 539

Email

ahmedmlaouhia6@gmail.com

Address

Soukra, Ariana, Tunisia

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mrboh https://github.com/ahmedmlaouhia https://gitlab.com/ahmedmlaouhia

Skills

- DevOps: Linux, Docker, Jenkins, CI/CD, Prometheus, Grafana...
- Web: React, Angular, Tailwind CSS, Daisy UI Typescript, Spring boot, Symfony, NET..
- Data Analysis
- Software Development cycle
- Git, GitLab, GitHub
- Agile Scrum Teamwork

Interests

- photography/Editing
- Video Games
- New technologies

Languages

- Arabic
- English
- French
- Germany

Reference

Ridha BEN RHOUMA

CTO, STARTNOW

Phone: +33 6 68 56 34 48 **Email:** rbr@start-now.fr

Experience

May 2023 - Present

Ariana - Remote

Start-Now

DevOps Engineeer - Part-time

Migrated the Infrastructure From OVH to AWS, Enhancing the Reliability, Security, Availability, Scalability and Performance Technologies: Linux, SSH, Docker, Jenkins, AWS EC2, AWS S3

August 2022

Remote

Kefil

Full-stack - Freelance

Made a dynamic presentation website for a non profitable charity (Kefil) which includes Donation and projects organization. Technologies: React, Typescript, Tailwind CSS, Firebase.

Apr 2022 - juin 2022

Ariana - Hybrid

Start-Now

DevOps intern

Integrated DevOps in the environement leading Start-Now to reduce TTM, optimize costs and automate the development, deployment, monitoring of their projects and infrastructure.

Technologies: Linux, SSH, Docker, Jenkins, Prometheus, Grafana

Education

2019 - 2022

Ariana

Tek-Up University

Engineering Degree

Software engineering and information system

2022 - 2023

Rades

ISET Rades

Master's Degree

Business Intelligence

2019 - 2022

Bizerte

Faculty of sciences of bizerte

Bachelor's Degree

Software engineering and information system

Projects

SkillSpark

React + Tailwind CSS+ Spring boot+ symfony

Created a university project in collaboration a web application for connecting Companies with students to benefit the companies with fresh talents accuisition through solving their projects minor tasks and let the students use the skills they learn in real life projects.

YOPEX

React + Material UI

Created the frontend of a Linkedin alike project which participated in HULT PRIZE in Boston - US and it reached advanced ranks in finals.

E-commerce app

Java + Android Studio

Developed mobile application for an E-commerce website in university.